Loading...

×

Close

 [](https://www.wiline.com/)[WiLine Secures Blackrock Funding to Expand 10G FWA Nationwide](https://www.wiline.com/blog/wiline-secures-blackrock-funding-to-expand-10g-fwa-nationwide/)

    * Services
    * * By Type
    * * By Industry
    * * By Need

Privacy Policy
==============

### WiLine Networks Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.

When do we collect information?

WiLine collects information from you when you fill out a form, Open a Support Ticket or enter information on our site.

How does WiLine use your information?

We may use the information collected from you when you register, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

1. To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service enquiries.
  
3. To quickly process your transactions.
  
5. To follow up with them after correspondence. (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

How do we protect visitor information?

* WiLine does not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
* WiLine only provides articles and information about its services. We will never ask for credit card numbers or banking information through this website.
* WiLine uses regular Malware Scanning on our servers.

WiLine does not use SSL encription on its website because we do not process sensitive information like credit cards or personal passwords through our website. You should be aware that the information you enter in the website is not therefore encrypted.

Do we use 'cookies' in this website?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. They can be used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to:

\- Compile aggregate anonymous data through Google Analytics about site traffic and site interactions in order to better understand the needs of our customers and offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf (Google Analytics).

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won't affect the user's experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

However, you can still use our contact form and your client area should you choose to do so.

Third-party disclosure

WiLine does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

Third-party links

WiLine does not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

Google

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

WiLine uses Google Analytics tracking software on our website.

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Opting out:

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA)

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

According to CalOPPA WiLine agrees to the following:

* Users can visit our site anonymously.
* Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.
* Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
* Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes through our policy page, date of policy will be clearly displayed.
* Users are able to change their personal information:

* By emailing us
* By calling us

How does our site handle do not track signals?

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?

It's also important to note that WiLine does not allow third-party behavioral tracking.

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

WiLine does not and will never specifically market to children under 13.

Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

We will notify the users via email  
  
• Within 7 business days  
We will notify the users via in-site notification  
  
• Within 7 business days  

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:

* Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
* Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:

* NOT use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
* Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
* Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
* Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
* Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
* Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you should follow the instructions at the bottom of each email. WiLine will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

Contacting WiLine Networks Inc

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

104 Carnegie Center, Suite 201  
Princeton, New Jersey 08540  
USA  
email: webmaster@wiline.com  
phone: 1-888-494-5463  
Last reviewed on 2021-11-21  

About WiLine

* * *

* WiLine helps businesses of all sizes keep pace with the growing demands of the digital age with our enterprise-grade, high-speed business internet service, cloud voice solution, managed Wi-Fi service, SD-WAN offering, and managed cybersecurity solution. Businesses choose WiLine for the freedom and flexibility they need to be productive and thrive.
    
    WiLine is present in 45 states and over 610 markets and growing rapidly. For full network coverage map, please see [our network](https://www.wiline.com/network/coverage) page.

Silicon Valley Office

* * *

* 793, 5th Ave
    
    Redwood City, CA 94063

Talk to Sales

    * * *

    * * *

    * * *

    * * *

    * * *

    * * *

    * * *

    * * *
